Contact

ramaramdhani7466@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ ramaramdhani (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Laravel HTML

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

Rama Ramdhani

Full Stack Web Developer 11430

Summary

Hi, my name is rama ramdhani, i am 17 years old, i live in bogor, west java, i am someone who really likes creativity and interesting ideas, my hobbies are playing guitar, sports and playing billiards.

currently I am a new graduate from SMKS WIKRAMA BOGOR. there I followed my expertise as a programmer, I studied various basic, intermediate and high-level programming languages, such as HTML, CSS3, C++, PHP and many more, also I use sharing kinds of frameworks like laravel, and react, js.

Experience

Indonesia Halal Training and Education Center (IHATEC)
Web Developer
December 2021 - March 2022 (4 months)

Bogor, West Java, Indonesia

I had an internship at Indonesia Halal Training & Education Center (IHATEC) as a web developer to create a full stack web using the html, css, php and laravel 8 frameworks

Kejar.id Web Developer March 2021 - June 2021 (4 months) Bogor Timur, West Java, Indonesia

I took part in an internship program organized by CV.IDS and I worked on a web developer project as a front-end developer, and UI/UX on the Kejar.id website.

In making Front-end I use html, css, , php and use laravel framework. and in making UI/UX using figma software.

Education

SMK WIKRAMA BOGOR

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Web/Multimedia Management and Webmaster · (2021 - 2022)